[{
        "question": "1.Chief components of First Generation Computer are ?",
        "options": [
            "transistors",
            "vacum tubes and valvs",
            "integrated circuits",
            "semiconductors"
        ],
        "answers": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "2.Which Unit performs the Mathematical operations in CPU ? ",
        "options": [
            "Memory Unit",
            "Control Unit",
            "Input Output Unit",
            "Arithmetic Logical Unit"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "3.What is the Direction of the Address Buss ?",
        "options": [
            "Unidirectional",
            "Bidirectional",
            "Multidirectional",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "4.Which Computer Architecture is implemented in Cache memory ?",
        "options": [
            "Von Neumann's Architecture",
            "Harvard Architecture",
            "Instruction Set Architecture",
            "None of the above"

        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "5.Which Bus is the carried the Address from CPU to Memory ?",
        "options": [
            "Data Bus",
            "Control Bus",
            "Address Bus",
            "All of the above"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "6.Which of the following is the Primary or Main Memory of the CPU ?",
        "options": [
            "Registers",
            "Random Access Memory(RAM)",
            "Read Only Memory(ROM)",
            "semiconductors"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "7.The CPU has 8-bits instruction,the Opcode of that instruction is 3-bit remaining 5-bit are Information so what is the Maximum Opcode size ?",
        "options": [
            "3",
            "5",
            "8",
            "32"
        ],
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "8.The brain of the Computer System is ?",
        "options": [
            "ALU",
            "CPU",
            "Memory",
            "Control Unit"
        ],
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "9.Which Computer Architecture we are using in now a days computers ?",
        "options": [
            "Von Neumann's Architecture",
            "Harvard Architecture",
            "Princeton Architecture",
            "None of the above"
        ],
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "10.One millisecond is what ?",
        "options": [
            "1 second",
            "10th of a seconds",
            "100th of a seconds",
            "1000th of a seconds"
        ],
        "answer": 4
    }
]